Rayna Harris

□512-657-2964 | ☑rayna.harris@gmail.com | ★www.raynaharris.com | 匝raynamharris | Уraynamharris

Professional Summary

I am interested in a Mountain Host Supervisor or Manager position at Alpine. I know the mountain well because I worked as a Parking Supervisor for the last three winters and enjoy skiing and snowboarding all of Alpine's terrain. I have many years of experience in customer service, managing projects, and supervising small groups.

Education

The University of Texas at AustinPh.D. Cell and Molecular Biology2012 - 2017The University of Texas at AustinAustinB.S. BIOCHEMISTRY2002 - 2006

Employment

Crest Cafe Alpine Meadows, CA BARISTA AND CASHIER July 2023 - Present **Lake Tahoe Community College** South Lake Tahoe, CA ADJUNCT FACULTY, BIOLOGY DEPARTMENT Jan 2023 - June 2023 **River Ranch Lodge and Restaurant** Alpine Meadows, CA HOSTESS Aug 2021 - Present **Palisades Tahoe - Alpine** Alpine Meadows, CA PARKING SUPERVISOR Nov 2020 - Jul 2023 **Rock & Rose Nursery + Landscaping** Truckee, CA NURSERY ASSISTANT Jun 2020 - Oct 2021 University of California, Davis Davis, CA POSTDOCTORAL SCHOLAR May 2018 - Apr 2023 The University of Texas at Austin Austin, TX LABORATORY MANAGER Oct 2010 - Sep 2012 The University of Texas at Austin Austin, TX TEACHING SPECIALIST Jan 2007 - Dec 2010

Computer Skills

Excel, HTML, LaTeX, Outlook, PowerPoint, Python, R, Square, TouchBistro, UNIX, Word

Languages Spoken __

English, Spanish

Honors and Awards

AAAS COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT FELLOWSHIP

RSTUDIO::CONF 2019 DIVERSITY SCHOLARSHIP

OUTSTANDING GRADUATE STUDENT ACADEMIC EMPLOYEE AWARD

UNIVERSITY GRADUATE CONTINUING FELLOWSHIP

ACADEMIC ENRICHMENT FUND AWARD

2014, 15, 16